ED
Q.What is your future goal?
A.I thought I would be a nuisance to everyone at the school because my voice would carry,
I always practice in the room where I do muscle training in the spring tours, like at the Erine.
I go there to practice.
Q. What did you eat yesterday?
A. It was a kind of crepe made with fresh cream that is only sold here. It was sold at a convenience store.
I bought it yesterday.
I was going to eat it last night, but I thought it was too dangerous to eat crepes at night,
So I decided not to eat it yesterday. I ate it in the morning.
Q. What are you eating these days?
A.I can't eat anything sweet today because I've been eating too many sweets lately.
I will try my best not to be sent.
Good luck with good feelings.
You too.
One each?
I wanted to eat. One more.
There's happiness.
I'm Mimahiko Kato. Please.
Thank you. Please.
Carnon is from this side.
I'll have him pull it for you.
I'll let you pull me.
Where are we?
Hiroshima!
We are Emichu!
Emichu! Bite!
But that's okay, we'll search together today.
I'm not doing so well here lately.
Apology Signal
I'm not being nice, but I'd rather say
I love you
You're being serious today.
I mean it, I'm crying.
You don't know what your siren means.
You don't know what it means to create.
All right, all right, all right, all right, all right.
Unsummified Bed Bee Styer...
Thank you very much.
I was doing vocal exercises on top of 5 lessons,
Aya on the first floor told me she heard voices.
What does that mean?